> > Jem Young: 现在我们在第三部分，让我们来设置这个服务器。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Now we're on part three,
let's set up that server.
所以当名称更改在互联网上传播的时候
So while the name changes
are propagating across the Internet,
让我们先设置我们的服务器，以便它现在能够处理一些请求。
let's set up our servers so
it can actually handle some requests now.
>> Jem Young: 基本上，步骤是，我们将更新软件。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Essentially, the steps are,
we're gonna update the software.
我们希望创建一个不是 root用户的新用户。
We want to create a new
user who's not root.
我们希望使该用户成为超级用户。
We want to make that user a super user.
我们希望允许该用户能够登录
We want to enable allow that
user to be able to login so
我们不需要登录到线路就可以过去了
we don't have to login to the route and
switch over.
然后，我们希望禁用 root 用户登录。
And then we want to disable root login.
您总是希望禁用 root 用户登录。
You always want to disable root login.
根本不需要以 root用户身份登录。
There's never a need to login as root.
它只会让自己受到更多的攻击。
It will only expose
yourself to more attacks.
如果我可以说攻击我会叫他们攻击
If, I could say attacks,
I'll call them attacks.
有人试图登录，但被归类为攻击。
There are people trying to log in but
they're classified as attacks.
我列出了这样的步骤，因为下一个是很多命令。
And I list out the steps like this because
the next bit is a lot of commands.
所以我要慢慢地去，但它是这里的所有终端。
So I'll go really slowly but
it's all terminal from here.
好，我们首先要做的就是要更新软件。
All right, first thing we wanna
do is we want to update software.
我们在用 ATP
We're using ATP.
如果您是在因特网上的教程或之前的教程，
If you're following tutorial on
the Internet or have before,
你可能是在用恰当的方法
you're probably using apt get.
APT 是一个包装在应用程序 get 和 app 的包装器，我认为可能是现金。
APT is a wrapper around app get and
app I think cash maybe.
但这是一种更简单的做法。
But it's a simpler way of doing abt.
这只是国家防范机制的一个软件包
It's just think of NPM in terms of
it's a software package of how to
下载软件。
download software.
所以我们现在仍然是一个根，但我们还是要更新软件。
So we're still a root at this point but
let's go and update the software.
因此，运行适当的更新，然后在软件更新后，可能需要一分钟。
So run apt update and then once a software
is updated, it might take a minute.
运行适当的升级。
Run apt upgrade.
>> 扬声器 2: 因此，我刚才退出了 root 用户。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So,
I exited out of root a while ago.
>> Jem Young: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Just, yeah.
所以请重新登录服务器， >> Jem Young: And
So log back into your server,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
退出服务器的方式是退出的。
the way to get out of a server is exit.
如果切换用户，那么可以退出然后再次退出，因此
And if you switch user,
you can exit and then exit again, so
它会把你送回根然后你就会退出
it's gonna drop you back to root and
then you're gonna exit.
所以我也要把这些都给跑了
So I'm gonna run those as well.
我要做的第一件事就是重新登录
First thing I'm gonna do is,
I'm gonna log back in.
我还应该注意，如果你在终端不知道，你就可以上去了
I should also note that if you didn't know
in the terminal, you can just go up or
就能从你的历史中恢复
down to go back through your history.
如果你想知道我是怎么输入的
I will use that a lot if
you're wondering how I type so
快速的原因是我正穿越我的历史
fast is because I'm just
traversing back up my history,
我只会以树根身份登录我就会有最新的更新
and I'm just gonna login as roots,
and I'm gonna run apt updates.
>> Jem Young: 并更新我的所有软件。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
updating all my software.
我要做升级改造
And I'm gonna run apt upgrade,
只是为了确保我在最新版本的东西上
just to make sure I'm on
the latest versions of things.
我想说对
And I'm gonna say, yes.
>> Jem Young: 通常，您总是希望使软件保持最新状态。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: In general, you always
want to keep your software up to date.
实际上是谁
In fact, who was it?
各位，我忘了昨天刚发生的事，我在看新闻。
So folks, I forget who there is just
happened yesterday I was reading the news.
有个保安公司说他们
There is a security provider that they,
就像赛门铁克 - 诺顿之类的
it was like the equivalent of
Symantec Norton or something like that.
他们是安全的大名之一他们被黑了
They're one of the big names in
security and they got hacked.
因为他们的论坛软件就像两年前的那样，或者我很抱歉，
Because their forum software was like
two years out of date or I'm sorry,
那不是两年了是两天之后的一天
it wasn't two years,
it was two days out of date.
他们为论坛所使用的 VB Bolton 软件中存在漏洞。
There's a vulnerability in the VB Bolton
software they used for the forum.
这个论坛被黑了，因为他们的软件一直没有更新。
The forum got hacked because they
didn't keep their software up to date.
你会发现的所有漏洞都来自
Almost all vulnerabilities
you'll find are from,
不是来自州的演员或者被确定要进入你的软件的人
are not from like state actors or people
determined to get into your software or
确定要到达您的服务器。
determined to get to your server.
因为你有一些软件
It's because you have some software.
该软件进行通信，
That software communicates,
应用程序与因特网进行通信。
the application communicates
with the Internet.
而那些应用程序也有漏洞。
And those that application
has vulnerabilities in it.
因此，您总是希望使软件保持最新状态。
So you always want to keep
your software up to date.
如果我在密码中使用 SSH 以外的任何安全提示。
If I give you any security tip
besides using SSH over a password.
这会让你的软件保持最新状态
It's keeping your software up to date.
你大部分时间都会没事的
You'll be fine most of the time.
我要用包裹维护人员的版本
I'm gonna use the package
maintainer's version.
因为我以后升级的时候可以同步
Because that way I can when I
upgrade later it will be in sync
无论他们推荐什么，都是根据盒子安装的。
with whatever they recommend versus
whatever was installed based on the box.
> > Jem Young: 现在我们应该好好的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And we should be good now.
我从所有人后面开始我就完了
I started behind everybody and I'm done.
所以希望大家都能做到。
So hopefully everybody else is done.
我们要加一个用户
We're gonna add a user.
通常这是需要使用的，那么我们已经是 root 用户了
Normally this would require using,
well we're already root so
我们不需要做什么之类的事
we don't have to do sudo or
anything like that.
好吧，让我们想想你想用的用户名。
All right, so
let's think of a username you want to use.
我们现在就用这个破折号
And we're gonna use the add the dash now.
添加用户，我就会说 jem.
Add user, I'm just gonna say jem.
如果需要，可以使用 jem 。
You can use jem if you want.
我不会冒犯并创建新的 UNIX 密码。
I'm not gonna be offended and
create a new UNIX password.
我要用很短的时间因为我们要打字
I'm gonna use something really short
because we're gonna be typing a lot and
我们就用另一个短的
we'll use another short one.
你可以把这玩意留到这里凉爽
You can leave it empty for
this stuff, cool.
因此，我确实使用用户名添加了用户。
So I did add user with the user name.
我把密码放进去，然后把所有东西都放在空白里。
I put in a password and then I just
put in the blanks for everything else.
如果需要，可以输入全名，根号。
You can put in the full name,
root number if you want.
是你的服务器
It's your server.
我不会告诉你怎么运作的
I'm not gonna tell you how to run it.
其实我要告诉你怎么做
Actually, I will tell you how to run it.
这就是我现在要做的
That's literally what I'm doing now.
但你可以为所欲为
But you can put in whatever you want for
this part.
这不重要
It doesn't matter.